# Ny Antsa Rajaonarison

Salesforce Developer

Lincoln Park, NJ

Linkedin | Trailhead

510-541-9835 nyantsa.rajaonarison@gmail.com 8X Salesforce Certified | 3 ☆Ranger

.....

Collaborative and detail-focused Salesforce Developer with 5 years of experience in implementing and customizing Salesforce Clouds. Skilled in gathering business requirements, configuring Salesforce, and developing Apex code and Lightning Web Components. Strong knowledge of Service Cloud, data security, and agile methodologies. Collaborates effectively with stakeholders and end-users to ensure successful project outcomes.

## **Employment history**

#### SLALOM | Salesforce Developer | New York, USA

Sep 2022 - Present

- Collaborated closely with business partners to gather, strategize, and analyze the business requirements for the successful implementation of different Clouds.
- Demonstrated expertise in Salesforce configuration, utilizing declarative tools available out-of-the-box, and customized processes using Apex coding, triggers, and LWC.
- Worked closely with developers to implement effective solutions following best practices.
- Contributed to the quality assurance process by actively identifying and resolving bugs, and collaborating with the QA team to reproduce and validate them, ensuring accurate and detailed fixes.
- · Focused on Service Cloud implementation and developed Service Cloud Voice with Amazon Connect
- Run Scrum rituals.

#### COGNIZANT | Salesforce Developer | New Jersey, USA

Feb 2020 - Sep 2022

- Collaborated with stakeholders and end-users to identify and define business requirements to implement Salesforce Service Cloud.
- Developed and maintained customized solutions within the Salesforce Service Cloud platform using out-of-the-box features as well as Apex and LWC.
- Designed and implemented Salesforce data models, objects, business automation, and data security to ensure the efficiency and accuracy of data management processes.
- · Worked closely with stakeholders to gather requirements and translated them into user stories
- Operated as a Scrum Master

#### THALES | Project Manager | Paris, France

Jan 2018 - Feb 2019

- Managed two teams working on minimum valuable product
- Ensured effective communication and collaboration between cross-functional teams to ensure project success
- Collaborated with members of the Product, Business and Engineering Teams to develop and maintain Product Backlogs
- Made sure the team lives by the values and practices of Scrum
- Facilitated release planning, sprint planning, backlog grooming and retrospective meetings
- Planned and defined Scope

#### **BNP Paribas | Intern Scrum Master | Paris, France**

Jun 2017 - Dec 2017

- Assisted in conducting Scrum team meetings and facilitating discussion and decision-making processes.
- Worked on DevOps accompaniment and assisted as an assistant project manager
- Integrated clients by understanding their needs in the DevOps process
- Planned and defined scope with clients
- Ensured the team followed the values and practices of Scrum
- Facilitated daily stand-up meetings and ensured timely delivery of tasks by the team

### **Education**

#### AWS, Online program | Certificate program in AWS

AWS Skill Builder program focusing on AWS services and implementation (continuing education)

#### Quintrix, Jersey City, NJ | Apprenticeship Salesforce Developer

Training that leads to employment opportunities in Salesforce development. Focused on Salesforce out-of-the-box features and Apex code.

#### General Assembly, San Francisco, CA | Software Engineer Immersive Program

Graduated from an intensive coding program with a concentration on web development. Emphasizing the MERN stack, along with proficiency in Python and Django.

#### University of Berkeley Extension

Topics: Databases, Java, Networking, Computer science

#### IONIS-Stm, Paris, France | Master Degree - Information System and Technology

Focused in project Management in the IT field

IAE-Poitiers, Poitiers, France | Master Degree - International Business

### **Certifications**

Salesforce Administrator I Salesforce Sharing and Visibility Architect

Salesforce Developer I Salesforce Platform App Builder

Salesforce Developer II Salesforce Omnistudio Consultant

Salesforce Service Cloud Salesforce Al Associate

## Languages

English (Highly proficient) French (Native)

Malagasy (Native)